(this["webpackJsonpquiz-stage2"]=this["webpackJsonpquiz-stage2"]||[]).push([[0],{13:function(e,t,o){},15:function(e,t,o){},16:function(e,t,o){"use strict";o.r(t);var n=o(1),i=o.n(n),a=o(4),s=o.n(a),r=(o(13),o(5)),c=o(6),u=o(8),l=o(7),d=o(2),p=o(0),h=function(e){Object(u.a)(o,e);var t=Object(l.a)(o);function o(){var e;return Object(r.a)(this,o),(e=t.call(this)).nextQues=function(){e.state.indexValue<15&&e.setState({indexValue:e.state.indexValue+1})},e.previousQues=function(){e.state.indexValue>0&&e.setState({indexValue:e.state.indexValue-1})},e.quit=function(e){e.preventDefault(),alert("Wait for Result")},e.state={indexValue:0},e}return Object(c.a)(o,[{key:"render",value:function(){return Object(p.jsx)("div",{className:"main-container",children:Object(p.jsxs)("div",{className:"quiz-container",children:[Object(p.jsx)("h1",{children:"Question"}),Object(p.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-container",children:[Object(p.jsxs)("h4",{children:[d[this.state.indexValue].id," of 15"]}),Object(p.jsx)("h3",{children:d[this.state.indexValue].question})]}),Object(p.jsxs)("div",{className:"options",children:[Object(p.jsx)("button",{children:d[this.state.indexValue].optionA}),Object(p.jsx)("button",{children:d[this.state.indexValue].optionB}),Object(p.jsx)("button",{children:d[this.state.indexValue].optionC}),Object(p.jsx)("button",{children:d[this.state.indexValue].optionD})]}),Object(p.jsxs)("div",{className:"buttons",children:[Object(p.jsx)("button",{onClick:this.previousQues,children:"Previous"}),Object(p.jsx)("button",{onClick:this.nextQues,children:"Next"}),Object(p.jsx)("button",{onClick:this.quit,children:"Quit"})]})]})})}}]),o}(n.Component);o(15);var m=function(){return Object(p.jsx)(h,{})},b=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&o.e(3).then(o.bind(null,17)).then((function(t){var o=t.getCLS,n=t.getFID,i=t.getFCP,a=t.getLCP,s=t.getTTFB;o(e),n(e),i(e),a(e),s(e)}))};s.a.render(Object(p.jsx)(i.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(p.jsx)(m,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),b()},2:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"id":1,"question":"Where is the Central Rice Research Institute located","optionA":"Bengaluru","optionB":"Kanpur","optionC":"Coimbator","optionD":"Cuttuck","answer":"Cuttuck"},{"id":2,"question":"Which one is India\'s first satellite exclusively used for educational purpose","optionA":"SARAL","optionB":"RISAT-1","optionC":"HAMSAT","optionD":"EDUSAT","answer":"EDUSAT"},{"id":3,"question":" Which one is India\'s First Indigenous Satellite Launch Vehicle","optionA":"PSLV","optionB":"ASLV","optionC":"GSLV","optionD":"SLV-3","answer":"SLV-3"},{"id":4,"question":"Who is known as the father of indian nuclear programme","optionA":"APJ Abdul Kalam","optionB":"Raja Ramanna","optionC":"Homi J Bhabha","optionD":"Vikram Sarabhai","answer":"Homi J Bhabha"},{"id":5,"question":"What is the full name of FAT?","optionA":"File attribute table","optionB":"File allocation table","optionC":"Font attribute table","optionD":"Format allocation table","answer":"File allocation table"},{"id":6,"question":"What is the mean of the Booting in the operating system?","optionA":"Restarting computer","optionB":"Install the program","optionC":"To scan","optionD":"To turn off","answer":"Restarting computer"},{"id":7,"question":"Banker\'s algorithm is used?","optionA":"To prevent deadlock","optionB":"To deadlock recovery","optionC":"To solve the deadlock","optionD":"None of these","answer":"To prevent deadlock"},{"id":8,"question":"The National Academy of Sciences, India is founded in the year","optionA":"1920","optionB":"1930","optionC":"1945","optionD":"1956","answer":"1930"},{"id":9,"question":"Which is the Linux operating system?","optionA":"Private operating system","optionB":"Windows operating system","optionC":"Open-source operating system","optionD":"None of these","answer":"Open-source operating system"},{"id":10,"question":"What is the full name of the DSM?","optionA":"Direct system module","optionB":"Direct system memory","optionC":"Demoralized system memory","optionD":"Distributed shared memory","answer":"Distributed shared memory"},{"id":11,"question":"What is the full name of the IDL?","optionA":"Interface definition language","optionB":"Interface direct language","optionC":"Interface data library","optionD":"None of these","answer":"Interface definition language"},{"id":12,"question":"Where the Headquater of National Academy of Sciences, India is located","optionA":"Delhi","optionB":"Kolkata","optionC":"Pune","optionD":"Allahabad","answer":"Allahabad"},{"id":13,"question":"What is the fence register used for?","optionA":"To disk protection","optionB":"To CPU protection","optionC":"To memory protection","optionD":"None of these","answer":"To memory protection"},{"id":14,"question":"Which of the following is a single-user operating system?","optionA":"Windows","optionB":"MAC","optionC":"Ms-Dos","optionD":"None of these","answer":"Ms-Dos"},{"id":15,"question":"India\'s first satellite Aryabhata was from","optionA":"Soviet Union","optionB":"America","optionC":"India","optionD":"Israel","answer":"Soviet Union"}]')}},[[16,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.fd11388e.chunk.js.map